<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Notes on English Reading Club</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/</link><description>Recent content in Notes on English Reading Club</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 09:55:14 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Book 18 Sessions 5</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-sessions-5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 09:55:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-sessions-5/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="notes">Notes&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-7-the-lord-will-provide">Chapter 7: The Lord Will Provide&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>His father is calm&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Treatment is very simple.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-8-tiny-harlots">Chapter 8: Tiny Harlots&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated/chapter-8-tiny-harlots" target="_blank">
Litcharts - Chapter Summary &amp;amp; Analysis
&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>har·lot | ˈhärlət | &lt;strong>noun&lt;/strong> &lt;em>archaic&lt;/em> a prostitute.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>• dated, derogatory a woman who has many casual sexual encounters or relationships.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h3 id="playing-piano">Playing Piano&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“People at church said Mary could play the piano beautifully. They used the word “professional.” I didn’t know what that meant until one Sunday when Mary played a piano solo for the congregation. The music stopped my breath. I’d heard the piano played countless times before, to accompany hymns, but when Mary played it, the sound was nothing like that formless clunking. It was liquid, it was air. It was rock one moment and wind the next.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The next day, when Mary returned from the school, I asked her if instead of money she would give me lessons. We perched on the piano bench and she showed me a few finger exercises. Then she asked what else I was learning besides the piano. Dad had told me what to say when people asked about my schooling. “I do school every day,” I said.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Tara is talented in music, and like music a lot.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Very curious&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Give up a bit of money&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="dancing">Dancing&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“She’d misunderstood. She thought I didn’t have money. “It isn’t modest,” I said. Her lips parted in surprise. These Californian Moyles, I thought.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Modest:&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“The other girls rarely spoke to me, but I loved being there with them. I loved the sensation of conformity. Learning to dance felt like learning to belong. I could memorize the movements and, in doing so, step into their minds, lunging when they lunged, reaching my arms upward in time with theirs. Sometimes, when I glanced at the mirror and saw the tangle of our twirling forms, I couldn’t immediately discern myself in the crowd. It didn’t matter that I was wearing a gray T-shirt—a goose among swans. We moved together, a single flock.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Tara got connected with other people (social people)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Not isolated, being in a group of people&lt;/li>
&lt;li>a goose among swans&lt;/li>
&lt;li>belonging&lt;/li>
&lt;li>自卑 not confident&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“The music ended. The girls glared at me as we left the stage—I had ruined the performance—but I could barely see them. Only one person in that room felt real to me, and that was Dad. I searched the audience and recognized him easily. He was standing in the back, the lights from the stage flickering off his square glasses. His expression was stiff, impassive, but I could see anger in it.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>The dad had a great influence on her.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Because of her father&amp;rsquo;s presence&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Maybe a disater&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Honorable girl, still managed&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Parent are not aware of their mistakes. (saving her daughter)&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“The rest of the night was taken up by my father’s lecture. He said Caroline’s class was one of Satan’s deceptions, like the public school, because it claimed to be one thing when really it was another. It claimed to teach dance, but instead it taught immodesty, promiscuity. Satan was shrewd, Dad said. By calling it “dance,” he had convinced good Mormons to accept the sight of their daughters jumping about like whores in the Lord’s house. That fact offended Dad more than anything else: that such a lewd display had taken place in a church.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Dance suit, should be modest&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Satan was shrewd&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“On the Wednesday after Caroline called Mother, I arrived at Papa Jay’s a few minutes early. The younger class had just finished, and the store was flooded with six-year-olds, prancing for their mothers in red velvet hats and skirts sparkling with sequins of deep scarlet. I watched them wiggle and leap through the aisles, their thin legs covered only by sheer tights. I thought they looked like tiny harlots.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h3 id="singing">Singing&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“MOTHER MUST HAVE FELT guilty after the recital, because in the weeks that followed she searched for something else I could do, something Dad wouldn’t forbid. She’d noticed the hours I spent in my room with Tyler’s old boom box, listening to the Mormon Tabernacle Choir, so she began looking for a voice teacher. It took a few weeks to find one, and another few weeks to persuade the teacher to take me. The lessons were much more expensive than the dance class had been, but Mother paid for them with the money she made selling oils.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>She loved the girl, and tried her best to help her daughter.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>mindful about&lt;/li>
&lt;li>paying very high attention on her daughter&lt;/li>
&lt;li>balance very well&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“Mother played the introduction. The music paused; it was time to sing. I might have had any number of thoughts at that moment. I might have thought of my teacher and her techniques—square stance, straight back, dropped jaw. Instead I thought of Tyler, and of lying on the carpet next to his desk, staring at his woolen-socked feet while the Mormon Tabernacle Choir chanted and trilled. He’d filled my head with their voices, which to me were more beautiful than anything except Buck’s Peak.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“Dad smiled at everyone. There was scarcely a person in the church that Dad hadn’t called a gentile—for visiting a doctor or for sending their kids to the public school—but that day he seemed to forget about California socialism and the Illuminati. He stood next to me, a hand on my shoulder, graciously collecting compliments. “We’re very blessed,” he kept saying. “Very blessed.” Papa Jay crossed the chapel and paused in front of our pew. He said I sang like one of God’s own angels. Dad looked at him for a moment, then his eyes began to shine and he shook Papa Jay’s hand like they were old friends.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Very big success&lt;/li>
&lt;li>totally different from the dancing&lt;/li>
&lt;li>church event&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“I’ll find the money,” he told Mother when they went to bed that night. “You get her to that audition.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-9-perfect-in-his-generation">Chapter 9: Perfect in His Generation&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated/chapter-9-perfect-in-his-generations" target="_blank">
LitCharts - Summary and Analysis
&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="dad-called-it-y2k">Dad called it Y2K.&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“The summer I sang the lead for Annie it was 1999. My father was in serious preparedness mode. Not since I was five, and the Weavers were under siege, had he been so certain that the Days of Abomination were upon us.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Dad called it Y2K. On January 1, he said, computer systems all over the world would fail. There would be no electricity, no telephones. All would sink into chaos, and this would usher in the Second Coming of Christ.
”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“Can’t they fix it?”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>“Nope, can’t be done,” Dad said. “Man trusted his own strength, and his strength was weak.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h3 id="at-the-worm-creek-opera-house">At the Worm Creek Opera House&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“I’d never learned how to talk to people who weren’t like us—people who went to school and visited the doctor. Who weren’t preparing, every day, for the End of the World. Worm Creek was full of these people, people whose words seemed ripped from another reality. That was how it felt the first time the director spoke to me, like he was speaking from another dimension. All he said was, “Go find FDR.” I didn’t move.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>He tried again. “President Roosevelt. FDR.”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>“Is that like a JCB?” I said. “You need a forklift?”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Everyone laughed.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h3 id="a-friend-called-charlies">A friend called Charlies&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“I’m Charles,” he said. There was a pause while he waited for me to give my name, but I didn’t. “I saw you in the last play,” he said after a moment. “I wanted to tell you something.” I braced myself, for what I wasn’t sure, then he said, “I wanted to tell you that your singing is about the best I ever heard.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“Maybe,” I said, and he smiled. A few of his friends stepped into the wing and called to him. He stood and said goodbye, and I watched him join them, taking in the easy way they joked together and imagining an alternate reality in which I was one of them. I imagined Charles inviting me to his house, to play a game or watch a movie, and felt a rush of pleasure. But when I pictured Charles visiting Buck’s Peak, I felt something else, something like panic. What if he found the root cellar? What if he discovered the fuel tank? Then I understood, finally, what the rifle was for. That mighty barrel, with its special range that could reach from the mountain to the valley, was a defensive perimeter for the house, for our supplies, because Dad said we would be driving when everyone else was hotfooting it. We would have food, too, when everyone else was starving, looting. Again I imagined Charles climbing the hill to our house. But in my imagination I was on the ridge, and I was watching his approach through crosshairs.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h3 id="y2k-problem-didnt-happen">Y2K problem didn&amp;rsquo;t happen&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>I waited for the screen to flicker and die. I was trying to take it all in, this last, luxurious moment—of sharp yellow light, of warm air flowing from the heater. I was experiencing nostalgia for the life I’d had before, which I would lose at any second, when the world turned and began to devour itself.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The longer I sat motionless, breathing deeply, trying to inhale the last scent of the fallen world, the more I resented its continuing solidity. […] Sometime after 1:30 I went to bed. I glimpsed Dad as I left, his face frozen in the dark, the light from the TV leaping across his square glasses.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>He seemed smaller to me than he had that morning. The disappointment in his features was so childlike, for a moment I wondered how God could deny him this. He, a faithful servant, who suffered willingly just as Noah had willingly suffered to build the ark.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But God withheld the flood.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="themes">Themes&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="devoutness-and-delusionhttpswwwlitchartscomliteducatedthemesdevoutness-and-delusion">&lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated/themes/devoutness-and-delusion" target="_blank">
Devoutness and Delusion
&lt;/a>&lt;/h3>
&lt;h3 id="family-abuse-and-entrapmenthttpswwwlitchartscomliteducatedthemesfamily-abuse-and-entrapment">&lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated/themes/family-abuse-and-entrapment" target="_blank">
Family, Abuse, and Entrapment
&lt;/a>&lt;/h3>
&lt;h3 id="memory-history-and-subjectivityhttpswwwlitchartscomliteducatedthemesmemory-history-and-subjectivity">&lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated/themes/memory-history-and-subjectivity" target="_blank">
Memory, History, and Subjectivity
&lt;/a>&lt;/h3>
&lt;h1 id="next-session">Next session&lt;/h1>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Homework: Finish Ch9, Ch10&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Host Volunteer: Samantha
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Questions&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Excerpts&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Book 18 Sessions 4</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-sessions-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 12:20:11 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-sessions-4/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="notes">Notes&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-5-honest-dirt">Chapter 5: Honest Dirt&lt;/h2>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>That pace would never be possible in the public school. You can only do that at home, where you can sit down and really focus, with no distractions.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Morse Code&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-6-shield-and-buckler">Chapter 6: Shield and Buckler&lt;/h2>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>I’d found a hard hat in the shop, but Dad took that, too. “You’ll move slower trying to balance this silly thing on your head,” he said.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h1 id="next-session">Next session&lt;/h1>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Homework: Finish Ch 7 - Ch9&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Host Volunteer: Jizu, Giselle&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Book 18 Session 3</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-session-3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 12:21:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-session-3/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="notes">Notes&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Chapter 3 &amp;amp; 4&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="grandam-over-in-town">Grandam-over-in-town&lt;/h2>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Faye forever removed and isolated herself - and her children - from her own family&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="taras-father-gene">Tara&amp;rsquo;s Father, Gene&lt;/h2>
&lt;h2 id="grandma-down-the-hill">Grandma-down-the-hill&lt;/h2>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“What was happening now had happened before. This was the second severing of mother and daughter. The tape was playing in a loop.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>diversity for the family members&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Illuminati &lt;a href="https://zh.wikipedia.org/wiki/%E5%85%89%E7%85%A7%E6%B4%BE" target="_blank">
光照派
&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“According to Grandma, a hundred years ago a tribe of Apaches had fought the U.S. Cavalry on those faded rocks. The tribe was outnumbered: the battle lost, the war over. All that was left to do was wait to die. Soon after the battle began, the warriors became trapped on a ledge. Unwilling to suffer a humiliating defeat, cut down one by one as they tried to break through the cavalry, they mounted their horses and charged off the face of the mountain. When the Apache women found their broken bodies on the rocks below, they cried huge, desperate tears, which turned to stone when they touched the earth.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-4">Chapter 4&lt;/h2>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“Me, I never blamed anyone for the accident, least of all Tyler. It was just one of those things. A decade later my understanding would shift, part of my heavy swing into adulthood, and after that the accident would always make me think of the Apache women, and of all the decisions that go into making a life—the choices people make, together and on their own, that combine to produce any single event. Grains of sand, incalculable, pressing into sediment, then rock.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h1 id="next-session">Next session&lt;/h1>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Homework: Finish Chapter 5 &amp;amp; 6&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Host Volunteer: Shuuka&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Book 18 Session 2</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-session-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 12:19:59 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-session-2/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="notes">Notes&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="q1-how-did-motherfatherme-get-changed-while-mother-became-a-midwife">Q1: How did Mother/father/me get changed while mother became a midwife?&lt;/h2>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Midwifing changed my mother. She was a grown woman with seven children, but this was the first time in her life that she was, without question or caveat, the one in charge. Sometimes, in the days after a birth, I detected in her something of Judy’s heavy presence, in a forceful turn of her head, or the imperious arch of an eyebrow. She stopped wearing makeup, then she stopped apologizing for not wearing it.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>At the beginning, very exhausted&lt;/li>
&lt;li>acted as an assistant&lt;/li>
&lt;li>acted as a midwife herself&lt;/li>
&lt;li>income/money to afford the telephone&lt;/li>
&lt;li>not so boring, help people&lt;/li>
&lt;li>cheaper but illegal&lt;/li>
&lt;li>only in charge&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Offered such a job under such circumstances, accept or not?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>age: 30 or 40 year-old?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>7 children, baby&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Her father really force her mother to work&lt;/li>
&lt;li>As long as we have income, then nobody can force us&lt;/li>
&lt;li>hesitated to make a change&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Every child is different&lt;/li>
&lt;li>stable&lt;/li>
&lt;li>She worked a housewife&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Why did she married such a kind of guy?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>妇产科 （Obstetrics and Gynecology） vs . Midwife&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Harvard Positive Psychology&lt;/li>
&lt;li>survivalist&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Dad stood there for several seconds, his mouth open. Of course a midwife needs a phone, he said. Then he went back to the junkyard and that’s all that was ever said about it. We hadn’t had a telephone for as long as I could remember, but the next day there it was, resting in a lime-green cradle, its glossy finish looking out of place next to the murky jars of cohosh and skullcap.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>She barked orders and we moved wordlessly to follow them. The baby was born without complications. It was mythic and romantic, being an intimate witness to this turn in life’s cycle, but Mother had been right, I didn’t like it. It was long and exhausting, and smelled of groin sweat.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="q2-how-can-we-learn-from-the-midwife-story-to-make-a-change-in-our-life">Q2: How can we learn from the midwife story to make a change in our life?&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Money is the most important thing.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>If you earn above an amount, doesn&amp;rsquo;t make a different. (Survey)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How to spend the money? For eating or helping others&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>The next time the midwife came she brought her daughter Maria, who stood next to her mother, imitating her movements, with a baby wedged against her wiry nine-year-old frame. I stared hopefully at her. I hadn’t met many other girls like me, who didn’t go to school. I edged closer, trying to draw her attention, but she was wholly absorbed in listening to her mother, who was explaining how cramp bark and motherwort should be administered to treat post-birth contractions. Maria’s head bobbed in agreement; her eyes never left her mother’s face.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>THERE WERE NO HERBALISTS in Wyoming as good as Mother, so a few months after the incident at the hospital, Judy came to Buck’s Peak to restock. The two women chatted in the kitchen, Judy perched on a barstool, Mother leaning across the counter, her head resting lazily in her hand. I took the list of herbs to the storeroom. Maria, lugging a different baby, followed. I pulled dried leaves and clouded liquids from the shelves, all the while gushing about Mother’s exploits, finishing with the confrontation in the hospital. Maria had her own stories about dodging Feds, but when she began to tell one I interrupted her.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>“Judy is a fine midwife,” I said, my chest rising. “But when it comes to doctors and cops, nobody plays stupid like my mother.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h1 id="next-session">Next session&lt;/h1>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Homework: ?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Host Volunteer: ?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Book 18 Session 1</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-session-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 12:19:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-session-1/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="game">Game&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>We split the 1st chapter into 3 parts, and 3 teams&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Team 1: Fancy, Ellen&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Team 2: Hongyan, Semantha&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Team 3: Giselle, Mia&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Online: Shuuka, Wendy&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="1st-part">1st part&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Until&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Then I remembered: the big dairy farm a mile north of Buck’s Peak, that was Jim’s.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Children should be guided by the god
Grandma: all children left except Tara' father&lt;/p>
&lt;p>How did Tara&amp;rsquo;s father get educated?
Mother&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Author&amp;rsquo;s father, education, public school&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Dream, imagination&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Religious&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Different versions&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Isaiah&lt;/li>
&lt;li>the solemnity of an oracle&lt;/li>
&lt;li>manicured&lt;/li>
&lt;li>As he slid past us I caught a whiff of manure.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mormons" target="_blank">
Mormons
&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="2nd-part">2nd part&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Until&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>then gunfire, then silence.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Grandma convince me to get away from my father&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Breakfast: seven kids&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Butter or honey&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Breakfast became a test of loyalty.
“Butter and honey shall he eat,” Dad droned, low and monotone, weary from a long day hauling scrap. “That he may know to refuse the evil, and choose the good.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>The next morning Dad purged our fridge of milk, yogurt and cheese, and that evening when he came home, his truck was loaded with fifty gallons of honey.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="3rd-part">3rd part&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Until the end of Chapter 1&lt;/p>
&lt;p>She didn&amp;rsquo;t leave finally.
Wounded Knee or Waco
for the Days of Abomination&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>They’re freedom fighters. They wouldn’t let the Government brainwash their kids in them public schools, so the Feds came after them.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://www.sparknotes.com/lit/educated/">https://www.sparknotes.com/lit/educated/&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated">https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h1 id="next-session">Next session&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Finish the 2nd chapter&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Book 17 Session 7</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-17-session-7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 12:19:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-17-session-7/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="watch-the-movie">Watch the movie&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Varonica and I were together.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Get two lovebirds home&lt;/li>
&lt;li>I&amp;rsquo;ll let you get settled.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Dylan Thomas&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Laykin&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="preview-the-movie">Preview the Movie&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://sap.sharepoint.com/teams/EnglishReadingClubChina/Shared%20Documents/Book%20Discussion/17th%20book%20The%20Sense%20of%20an%20Ending" target="_blank">
Click here
&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Book 17 Session 6</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-17-session-6/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 12:19:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-17-session-6/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="heading">&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>NEVER use the word &lt;code>retarded&lt;/code> (offensive)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Downs syndrome&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>that life is a gift bestowed without anyone asking for it; that the thinking person has a philosophical duty to examine both the nature of life and the conditions it comes with; and that if this person decides to renounce the gift no one asks for, it is a moral and human duty to act on the consequences of that decision.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Is Adrian a hypocritical person?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Tony admired the Adrian.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Robson committed suicide.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Irony&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Adrian committed suicided to show he should get punished?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Oedipus complex for Adrian&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Voronica&amp;rsquo;s mother: Mrs Ford&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>She had a somewhat artistic air&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Evidence ?&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Even her own mother warned me against her. If I were you, I’d check things out with Mum – ask her about damage a long way back. Of course, you’ll have to do this behind Veronica’s back, because boy is that girl a control freak.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Part of me hopes you’ll have a child, because I’m a great believer in time’s revenge, yea unto the next generation and the next.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Right: fucking bastards. Except to Adrian, who listened to our denunciations, but rarely joined in. And yet, it seemed to us, he had more cause than most. His mother had walked out years before, leaving his dad to cope with Adrian and his sister. This was long before the term ‘single-parent family’ came into use; back then it was ‘a broken home’, and Adrian was the only person we knew who came from one. This ought to have given him a whole storetank of existential rage, but somehow it didn’t; he said he loved his mother and respected his father. Privately, the three of us examined his case and came up with a theory: that the key to a happy family life was for there not to be a family – or at least, not one living together. Having made this analysis, we envied Adrian the more.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="title-of-the-book-the-sense-of-an-ending">Title of the book: The sense of an ending&lt;/h2>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>There is accumulation. There is responsibility. And beyond these, there is unrest. There is great unrest.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="for-next-session">For Next Session&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>本次没有额外reading assignment. 下周继续讨论和串联各种情节和细节，欢迎光临。&lt;/p>
&lt;p>我们或将组织一起看这部电影，请关注本群消息。&lt;/p>
&lt;p>下一本书Educated的团购准备工作也即将展开，请稍后。&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Apr 7 中午12:15，pvg12 11.4 或者线上见。&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Book 17 Session 5</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-17-session-5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 12:19:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-17-session-5/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="from-margaret">from Margaret&lt;/h2>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>‘No,’ she said. ‘I left you because of us.’&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>‘I don’t think the worse of you. I don’t even think the worse of the Fruitcake, though admittedly my estimation of her has always been below sea level.’&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Fruitcake: nickname for Voronica&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Why did Margaret check the bill?&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Margaret checked the bill, running the corner of her credit card down the items.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>crippy&lt;/p>
&lt;p>What are the clear motifs?&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="next-session">Next session&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Finish the book&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Book 17 Session 4</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-17-session-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 12:19:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-17-session-4/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="heading">&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Q1: Why did Tony met his ex-wife(Magarate)?
Voranica, Brother Jack
Fragment from Andrian&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>And as the poet pointed out, there is a difference between addition and increase.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>‘He took his own life’ is the phrase; but Adrian also took charge of his own life, he took command of it, he took it in his hands – and then out of them.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Graph&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>x-axis:&lt;/li>
&lt;li>y-axis:&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Boundary&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Retrospective&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Writing&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>OKR&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>main idea: let the people to control the life, but you set up the objective and key result&lt;/li>
&lt;li>combination between the top-down and bottom-up style&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Learning the OKR
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://www.whatmatters.com/articles/ted-talk/" target="_blank">
TedTalk with John Doerr
&lt;/a> 10min video&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://teams.microsoft.com/l/file/3CEA87E7-0F00-46A3-A772-5FA50FAB9B23?tenantId=42f7676c-f455-423c-82f6-dc2d99791af7&amp;amp;fileType=pdf&amp;amp;objectUrl=https%3A%2F%2Fsap.sharepoint.com%2Fteams%2FITECHLounge887%2FShared%20Documents%2FGeneral%2FOKR%2FMeasure-What-Matters.pdf&amp;amp;baseUrl=https%3A%2F%2Fsap.sharepoint.com%2Fteams%2FITECHLounge887&amp;amp;serviceName=teams&amp;amp;threadId=19:b9a347579f504658aaeb23d4879b36fa@thread.tacv2&amp;amp;groupId=a7b071f4-8950-4e08-b438-71e1eea67fae" target="_blank">
Measure what Matters
&lt;/a> (20min reading the book abstract&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://teams.microsoft.com/l/file/92FF75A0-15B3-48E1-838A-32A450485793?tenantId=42f7676c-f455-423c-82f6-dc2d99791af7&amp;amp;fileType=pdf&amp;amp;objectUrl=https%3A%2F%2Fsap.sharepoint.com%2Fteams%2FITECHLounge887%2FShared%20Documents%2FGeneral%2FOKR%2F20201102_OKRs%20at%20a%20glance_short.pdf&amp;amp;baseUrl=https%3A%2F%2Fsap.sharepoint.com%2Fteams%2FITECHLounge887&amp;amp;serviceName=teams&amp;amp;threadId=19:b9a347579f504658aaeb23d4879b36fa@thread.tacv2&amp;amp;groupId=a7b071f4-8950-4e08-b438-71e1eea67fae" target="_blank">
Objectives and Key Results (OKRs) @ S/4HANA team
&lt;/a>10min reading slides&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/learning/goal-setting-objectives-and-key-results-okrs/the-power-of-strategic-goals-objectives-and-key-results-okrs?u=57692769" target="_blank">
LinkedIn OKR Training
&lt;/a>30min training&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Tony met Magaret
Tony met Voronica
Why did Brother&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Tony suspects things, sensitive&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>‘The Fruitcake?’&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="next-session">Next session&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Read until&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Still, she had danced.
(p.115 paper book edition)&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Prepare for the poster for the next book, buy the book&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Book 17 Session 3</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-17-session-3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 12:19:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-17-session-3/</guid><description>&lt;p>Mar 10&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Tony get divorced, and felt lonely
Platonic girlfriends
Received a letter from a lawyer&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Tony &amp;amp; Veronica
Veronica&amp;rsquo;s mother
Adrian: committed suicide&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>we make an instinctive decision, then build up an infrastructure of reasoning to justify it. And call the result common sense. Did I think Adrian’s action an implied criticism of the rest of us?&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Memory differs from the old facts/reality
cowardice / peaceable
keeping diary&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Or perhaps it’s that same paradox again: the history that happens underneath our noses ought to be the clearest, and yet it’s the most deliquescent. We live in time, it bounds us and defines us, and time is supposed to measure history, isn’t it? But if we can’t understand time, can’t grasp its mysteries of pace and progress, what chance do we have with history – even our own small, personal, largely undocumented piece of it?&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>And it ought to be obvious to us that time doesn’t act as a fixative, rather as a solvent. But it’s not convenient – it’s not useful – to believe this; it doesn’t help us get on with our lives; so we ignore it.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="before-next-session">Before next session&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Read until p.93&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>I didn’t open the envelope Veronica gave me for a day and a half. I waited because I knew she would expect me not to wait, to have my thumb at the flap before she was out of sight.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote></description></item><item><title>Book 17 Session 2</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-17-session-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 12:19:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-17-session-2/</guid><description>&lt;p>Mar 3&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="briefing-about-20-to-40-page">Briefing about 20 to 40 page:&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Tony visited Veronica’s home for one weekend&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Veronica met Tony’s friend, including Adrian&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Tony slept with Veronica and split with her&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Veronica’s mother wrote a letter to Tony, didn’t blame Tony at all&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Adrian wrote letter to Tony ask for permission to go out with Veronica&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="what-is-veronicas-familys-opinion-on-tony">What is Veronica’s family’s opinion on Tony?&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>The father making jokes on Tony, a lot of negative words to describe, for example “lower-class scum”, shows that Tony didn’t like father;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The brother “He behaved towards me as if I were an object of …”, looks like both the father and the brother are looking down upon Tony;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The mother looks very different;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>One evidence by the author “This is my principal factual memory…” that the memory might be very different with the fact. So the reader should be very skeptical to what we read in this part.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Looks like Veronica is not treating Tony not very well. Veronica didn’t kiss Tony good evening. Join their examination. This might because Tony hate Veronica because Veronica went out with Adrian.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Contrary “I was expecting further examination …” but actually they are treating Tony very well “grew tired of me”&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="key-term-for-further-info">Key term for further info:&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Unreliable narrator , 举例：了不起的盖茨比&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://baike.baidu.com/item/%E5%8F%8D%E4%B8%BB%E6%B5%81%E6%96%87%E5%8C%96/7290804?fr=aladdin" target="_blank">
counterculture movement 反文化运动 1960s
&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="what-do-you-think-tony-as-a-boy-friend">What do you think Tony as a boy friend?&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>From Veronica, coward, keep asking what is the future of their relationship&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Irresponsible&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="why-they-split-up">Why they split up?&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Tony provide comment that he is very innocent.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>“After we broke up …” -&amp;gt; after the sex, Tony dumped Veronica&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Veronica mother’s letter to Tony&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>The letter is lost&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Imitating there is a court, set up like Tony is a criminal, reader is judge. Tony would like to demonstrate he is innocent, about P28, “I felt before a court…”,  about P35 “…a court of law…” “proof corroboration”.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Received the letter from Adrian, postponing tell the letter content, Tony provided a lot of ironic comment. Adrian studies Moral science 伦理学.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Photo with Veronica and Tony’s friends without Tony.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="return-to-first-paragraph">Return to first paragraph,&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>1st item: The shiny inner wrist – wear watch inside, make the time more personal, wear the watch outside&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="time-vs-history">Time vs history&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>2nd item: Steam rising from a wet sink… - the mother made Tony breakfast&lt;/li>
&lt;li>3rd item:&lt;/li>
&lt;li>4th item: a river before they slept they went to watch river 涨潮&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="about-the-author">About the author&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Born in 50s&lt;/li>
&lt;li>60s, 很多思潮，性自由等&lt;/li>
&lt;li>福楼拜的鹦鹉，成名作，非常创新&lt;/li>
&lt;li>大学学习法语，哲学，等&lt;/li>
&lt;li>参与用词精准的工作，比如non fiction，字典编撰&lt;/li>
&lt;li>写过四本detective story&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="next-session">Next session&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Until&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>‘In other words, don’t let her start thinking I’m some kind of loony.’&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote></description></item><item><title>Book 17 Session 1</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-17-session-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 12:19:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-17-session-1/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="until-page-20">Until page 20&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="background">Background&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>The author is famous: &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Julian_Barnes" target="_blank">
Julian Barnes
&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="questions">Questions&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Genre:
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>old man remembering novel,&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Campus:&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Main character: Tony&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="first-part">First part&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Jeff: A lot of the novel is about how memory is fallible&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Collage&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Expressions&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>If I can’t be sure of the actual events any more, I can at least be true to the impressions those facts left. That’s the best I can manage.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>History&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>What is History? Any thoughts, Webster?’
History is that certainty produced at the point where the imperfections of memory meet the inadequacies of documentation.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>New historicism: histories vs History &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_historicism" target="_blank">
Wiki
&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>BBC documentary: &amp;ldquo;Biased Broadcasting Chinese&amp;rdquo;
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>narration&lt;/li>
&lt;li>进击的巨人: Attack on Titan&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>materials&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Robson had got his girlfriend pregnant, hanged himself in the attic, and not been found for two days.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>野史&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Shall we really seek for the true fact (history)?
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>certain level of skepticism&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>uncertainty principle，又译测不准原理&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="next-session">Next session:&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Read until page 40&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>As you can imagine, I enjoyed the bit about his moral scruples &amp;hellip; Or rather, my memory now of my reading then of what was happening at the time.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote></description></item><item><title>Book 16 Practice Session 2</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-16-practice-session-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 12:26:06 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-16-practice-session-2/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="teams-1-sap-certification-team">Teams 1: SAP Certification team&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Leader: Shuuka&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Main goal: Get the certifications!&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Measure:
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>At least one cert during the 90 days&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Two parts
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Learning: OpenSAP, Learning Hub&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Review:&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Estimate efforts
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Free learning&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Recite 100 question?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Monitor each other, 0.5 hour per working day&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Outcomes
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Add to your profile, LinkedIn&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Coverage
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Azure, SAP &amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Design thinking, time management&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Choices
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>C4C Service&lt;/li>
&lt;li>BW&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Customer Service&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Design thinking (certified coach)&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="teams-2-chinese-poem-team">Teams 2: Chinese Poem team&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Leader: Hongyan&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Dream big, start small&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Finish reciting 27 poems in 90 days&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://sap.sharepoint.com/teams/EnglishReadingClubChina/_layouts/15/Doc.aspx?OR=teams&amp;amp;action=edit&amp;amp;sourcedoc=%7b4DC554A2-E537-49AC-B41F-C13CAF142152%7d" target="_blank">
Slides from Mia
&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;iframe src="https://sap.sharepoint.com/teams/EnglishReadingClubChina/_layouts/15/Doc.aspx?sourcedoc={4dc554a2-e537-49ac-b41f-c13caf142152}&amp;amp;action=embedview&amp;amp;wdAr=1.7777777777777777" width="610px" height="367px" frameborder="0">This is an embedded &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://office.com">Microsoft Office&lt;/a> presentation, powered by &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://office.com/webapps">Office&lt;/a>.&lt;/iframe>
&lt;h2 id="teams-3-swi-sports-writing-and-inspiration">Teams 3: SWI (Sports, Writing, and Inspiration)&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Leader: Giselle&lt;/li>
&lt;li>To be attached: Notion Notes taken with Jizu&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Giselle: Avoid driving to work, instead, cycle to work&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Reporting (打卡): Share something funny, interesting etc&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="impressive">Impressive&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Hongyan
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Shuuka team: actionable, clear target&lt;/li>
&lt;li>SWI: cycling, writing&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Jennifer (Guest)
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Like sports very much, keep practicing to swim&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Mia
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Eat one egg every day&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How to boil a perfect egg: wait for 5 min or more&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Sub-goal&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Thomas (Guest)
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Goals can be shared, members can join several&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Shuuka
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Didn&amp;rsquo;t recite poems for years&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Improve your life, culture, feelings&amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Giselle
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Each team is so inspiring&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Less is more&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Can communicate with each other&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="follow-up">Follow-up&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Set the checkpoint / target day&lt;/li>
&lt;li>To present how far we&amp;rsquo;re&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Create a wechat group for all&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Group TODO&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="plan-for-the-next-book">Plan for the next book&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Feb 24: start early&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Jizu follow up with Katniss&lt;/li>
&lt;li>More practice for the reading&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="recordings-from-ms-teams">Recordings from MS Teams&lt;/h2>
&lt;div style='max-width: 853px'>&lt;div style='position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;'>&lt;iframe width="853" height="480" src="https://web.microsoftstream.com/embed/video/6d82ad7c-ee38-41ee-8d7d-11a6b9cb5f7a?autoplay=false&amp;amp;showinfo=true" allowfullscreen style="border:none; position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; right: 0; bottom: 0; height: 100%; max-width: 100%;">&lt;/iframe>&lt;/div>&lt;/div></description></item><item><title>Book 16 Practice Session 1</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-16-practice-session-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 12:26:54 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-16-practice-session-1/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="files">Files&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://sap.sharepoint.com/teams/EnglishReadingClubChina/Shared%20Documents/Book%20Discussion/16th%20book%20-%20The%2090%20Day%20Life" target="_blank">
Xmind files on SharePoint
&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="take-turns-to-represent-yourself">Take turns to represent yourself&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="1-mia-sap-learning-day">1. Mia: SAP Learning Day&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Eat boiled eggs&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="2-shuuka-to-get-a-sap-certification">2. Shuuka: to get a SAP certification&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>In SAP, you can take for free&lt;/li>
&lt;li>SAP welfare&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Tips from colleagues: question pool, three hours, 80 questions&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="3-mike-hands-on-for-sap-btp">3. Mike: Hands-on for SAP BTP&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Topics for certifications may varies&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Already passed some certifications, charging the cost center&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Hands-on can be found on the SAP developer portal (community?)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>25 missions, 1 to 2 hours per missions&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Will share the link after the session&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="4-hongyan-big-dream-group">4. Hongyan: Big dream group&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Raising child: you need to be a good parent&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Tangible goal: Recite Chinese old poem, 100 poem per year&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Trigger my children to recite more&lt;/li>
&lt;li>To dream big&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="5-giselle-prepare-for-the-summary">5. Giselle: Prepare for the summary&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Go to gym&lt;/li>
&lt;li>I need to really work hard today, tomorrow&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Skinning&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="6-jizu">6. Jizu&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Just crashed? Give another shot!&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Think about how we deal with a crashed computer, and think about what to do if our plan doesn&amp;rsquo;t go well
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Restart Yourself&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Bring Yourself back&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Ask for help&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h1 id="teams">Teams&lt;/h1>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Shuuka &amp;amp; Mia&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Mike &amp;amp; Hongyan&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Jizu &amp;amp; Giselle&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h1 id="just-crashed--give-it-a-3-step-fix">Just Crashed ? Give it a 3-step Fix!&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Author: &lt;a href="https://linkedin.com/in/jizusun" target="_blank">
Jizu SUN
&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This is a prepared speech in &lt;a href="https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-16-practice-session-1/">
this practice session
&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://english-reading-club.github.io/windows-10-bluescreen.png" alt="Windows 10 blue screen">&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Your PC run into a problem and need to restart. We&amp;rsquo;re just collecting some error info, and then you can restart.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://english-reading-club.github.io/macos-crash-1.png" alt="macOS crash screen">
&lt;img src="https://english-reading-club.github.io/macos-crash-2.png" alt="macOS crash screen">&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Your computer restarted because of a problem. Press a key or wait a few seconds to continue starting up.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Yesterday, in a WeChat group, we had such a great fun blaming and teasing the IT services in our company. Our IT installed various software to secure our computers, but it ended up making them crappy. Computers sometimes become unresponsive, sometimes even crashed. Crashed like a dog!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But I have to say, it is NOT our IT services to be blamed. The computer is such a complicated system, no matter it is a Windows laptop, a MacBook, or a Linux box, that the crash happened because of various root causes. Perhaps it&amp;rsquo;s a bug of the underlying operating system, perhaps it&amp;rsquo;s a compatibility problem that is brought by the applications you or the IT services just installed, 0r perhaps it&amp;rsquo;s just because your computer is in a bad mood! God knows!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But even if the computer crashes from time to time, you cannot give it up.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You need to face it! You just give it a shot to see if it can work after the reboot. If the crash happens again, you need to think a little more. Do you have any application recently installed? Do you have any system configuration changed? Uninstall the application or restore the configuration may fix the problem. If the problem persists, you might go to IT services for help.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you look into the Window 10 blue screen, it seems it collectes the error information before the restart. It seems a good idea, right? The software engineers need something to refer to.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You see, a computer crash annoys you, but it&amp;rsquo;s not a big problem.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>The easiest thing you can do is to restart your computer.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Even you don&amp;rsquo;t understand why it happens, you can try to revert it back, like uninstalling.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The final thing you can do is also easy, that is to find a nice guy to help you!&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Now coming back to our 90-day life challenge, you can do the same thing as you do for the computer crash.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>If your plan doesn&amp;rsquo;t go well, just &amp;ldquo;restart&amp;rdquo; yourself. Take a nap, take a shower, have a good meal. Anything enjoyable can bring you energy&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Even if you don&amp;rsquo;t understand why it happens, you can refer to your diary or your journal to, kind of, revert your life back.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The final thing you can do is also easy, that is to find somebody you really trust to help you out, your 90-day life buddy, your families, your close friends.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>You see, if your plan doesn&amp;rsquo;t go well, it&amp;rsquo;s not a big problem &amp;ndash; JUST give it another shot!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Book 17 Chapter 13</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-16-chapter-13/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 12:19:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-16-chapter-13/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="90-day-success-principles">90-day success principles&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="principle-1-your-mental-means-are-your-most-important-asset">Principle 1: Your mental means are your most important asset&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>What is &lt;code>mental means&lt;/code>?
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Mental means is your most important assets&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>financial means: Money is nothing if doubts holding you back.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>When sb. posted a negative comment, i moved past it&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Question: What if I don&amp;rsquo;t have mental means?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Question: Anybody who have strong mental means?
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Sales person&lt;/li>
&lt;li>One of my friend, a lawyer&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="principle-2-focus-on-being-present-with-yourself-rather-than-trying-to-be-perfect">Principle 2: Focus on Being Present with Yourself, Rather than Trying to Be Perfect&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Example
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>writing articles, you don&amp;rsquo;t have to make it perfect&lt;/li>
&lt;li>not a long articles&lt;/li>
&lt;li>My friend is writing articles&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Kickoff&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Jizu can make a promise to us&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Wait too much, but at the end you get nothing (or less)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Windows laptop or macbook?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="principle-3-be-accountable">Principle 3: Be Accountable&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Review at least once a week&lt;/li>
&lt;li>If you miss the goal, just brush it, let it go&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Book 16 Chapter 12</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-16-chapter-12/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 12:18:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-16-chapter-12/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="stage-by-stage-view">Stage by stage view&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Each stage includes 10 days&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="stage-1-plan-and-habit">Stage 1: Plan and habit&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Revisit the end result&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Calendar&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Rough plan for 5 years or so?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Mike: Learn S/4 HANA business domain knowledge, how customers use it(end result), not to get the certificate, but get to know more colleagues for this fields (more connections), can explain well when working with customers (measurement)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Shuuka: tools(systems) are replaceable&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="stage-2-create-novelty">Stage 2: Create novelty&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>different way to do it&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Brush the teeth in another way&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Jizu: Brush my teeth while sitting on the bed and enjoy it in the warmer bedroom&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Hongyan
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Use another side of your hand (less frequent one)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Meditation: while brushing your teeth&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Mia: in college, walk or pack my bag during the teeth-brushing&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Mike: How to commute to the company, usually take bus in the morning and take metro in the afternoon, part the car a little bit far away from the company&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="stage-3-take-courteous-action">Stage 3: Take Courteous Action&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Focus Area 3: Serve &amp;amp; Succeed&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="stage-4-seek-out-adventure">Stage 4: Seek out adventure&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Practice courage&lt;/li>
&lt;li>A small goal within 10 days&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In a different way&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Mia: suggestions on the dress-up&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Birthday gift
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Surprise (mike)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Worry about it&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Make it easy&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Not surprise but shock&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="stage-5-erase-resentment">Stage 5: Erase Resentment&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>First 5 day: someone to forgive&lt;/li>
&lt;li>resentment for trivial quarrels with mothers&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Say thank you to someone I don&amp;rsquo;t like who taught a lesson&lt;/li>
&lt;li>critism: internship 眼高手低 (have grandiose aims but puny abilities)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Make you stronger&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="stage-6-embrace-spontaneity">Stage 6: Embrace Spontaneity&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>5-second countdown&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Yesterday customer success summit&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="stage-7-minimize-your-potential-regrets">Stage 7: Minimize Your Potential Regrets&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="stage-8-practice-gratitude">Stage 8: Practice Gratitude&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Show gratitude for 5 things each day (Harvard Happiness Lesson)&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="final-exercise-gratitude">Final exercise: Gratitude&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Shuuka: Living in China&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Families who support you no matter where they are&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="attachment">Attachment&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>mind-map from Shuuka: &lt;a href="https://sap.sharepoint.com/teams/EnglishReadingClubChina/Shared%20Documents/Book%20Discussion/16th%20book%20-%20The%2090%20Day%20Life" target="_blank">
Click to browse
&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Chapter 11: The Four Life Areas - Book 16: The 90 Day Life</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-16-chapter-11/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 18:49:10 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-16-chapter-11/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="have-dreams-that-scare-you">Have Dreams that Scare You&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>To challenge yourself. If it is very difficult but you still want it, it means it is your real dream.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To be confident enough to face Uncertainty.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="discussion">Discussion:&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Mask has the dream to go to Mars&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="cite-from-the-book">Cite from the book:&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Page 127 not to put my life on the back burner.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Page 128 It was a strange feeling of absolute clarity about what I wanted – and absolute terror at the sheer thought of it.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Page 128 Beyond the fear is great joy. Beyond the uncertainty lies great clarity. Beyond the doubt lies great action.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="question">Question:&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Any dreams which can scare you?&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="four-areas">Four Areas&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Health is the first priority. Contribution comes only at 3rd place. Mental health.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Less is more.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Personal growth : Adventures&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="discussion-1">Discussion:&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>拍多多event&lt;/li>
&lt;li>996&lt;/li>
&lt;li>house wife - work life balance&lt;/li>
&lt;li>断舍离 for gifts&lt;/li>
&lt;li>穿搭组合 based on limited different 单品&lt;/li>
&lt;li>school uniform&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="cite-from-the-book-1">Cite from the book:&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>P136 Your ability to focus on “why” you do what you do, not just get lost in the “what” you must do to get the work done.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>P138 The bigger the fear, the more exciting the adventure on the other side and the bigger the reward.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h3 id="question-1">Question:&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Do you ever think about anything you want to do until you retire?&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>