<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Educated on English Reading Club</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/tags/educated/</link><description>Recent content in Educated on English Reading Club</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-GB</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 23:01:33 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://english-reading-club.github.io/tags/educated/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Book 18 Session 14</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-session-14/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 23:01:33 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-session-14/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="notes">Notes&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-34">Chapter 34&lt;/h2>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-35">Chapter 35&lt;/h2>
&lt;h1 id="next-session">Next session&lt;/h1>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Homework: Finish Ch36 - Ch38&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Host Volunteer: Mia &amp;amp; Shuuka&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Book 18 Session 13</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-session-13/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 23:01:31 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-session-13/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="notes">Notes&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-30">Chapter 30&lt;/h2>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-31">Chapter 31&lt;/h2>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-32">Chapter 32&lt;/h2>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-33">Chapter 33&lt;/h2>
&lt;h1 id="next-session">Next session&lt;/h1>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Homework: Finish Ch34 - Ch35&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Host Volunteer: Mia&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Book 18 Session 12</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-session-12/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 23:01:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-session-12/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="notes">Notes&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-25">Chapter 25&lt;/h2>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-26">Chapter 26&lt;/h2>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-27">Chapter 27&lt;/h2>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-28">Chapter 28&lt;/h2>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-29">Chapter 29&lt;/h2>
&lt;h1 id="next-session">Next session&lt;/h1>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Homework: Finish Ch30 - Ch33&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Host Volunteer: Jizu&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Book 18 Sessions 11</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-sessions-11/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 11:41:59 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-sessions-11/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="notes">Notes&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-22-what-we-whispered-and-what-we-screamed">Chapter 22: What We Whispered and What We Screamed&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated/chapter-22-what-we-whispered-and-what-we-screamed" target="_blank">
Summary and Analysis
&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Shawn wanted to humiliate Tara in front of Charles&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-23--im-from-idaho">Chapter 23: I’m From Idaho&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated/chapter-23-i-m-from-idaho" target="_blank">
Summary and Analysis
&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ruby_Ridge" target="_blank">
Ruby_Ridge
&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-24">Chapter 24&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated/chapter-24-a-knight-errant" target="_blank">
Summary and Analysis
&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="next-session">Next session&lt;/h1>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Homework: Finish the chapter 29&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Host Volunteer: Samatha &amp;amp; Mia&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h1 id="notes-1">Notes&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Charles didn’t stay for supper. He fled to his jeep and I didn’t hear from him for several hours, then he called and asked me to meet him at the church. He wouldn’t come to Buck’s Peak. We sat in his jeep in the dark, empty parking lot. He was crying.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>What was important to me wasn’t love or friendship, but my ability to lie convincingly to myself: to believe I was strong. I could never forgive Charles for knowing I wasn’t.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>He said he loved me but this was over his head. He couldn’t save me. Only I could.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>“Sorry, Siddle Lister, but it hurts less if you don’t see it coming.”&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>Only an X-ray could prove otherwise. Thus, the X-ray would break my toe.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>I was filled with an exquisite numbness. I felt drunk with it and wanted to shout at the world: Here’s the proof: nothing touches me.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>ichard was the miracle son, the gift from God, the Einstein to disprove Einstein. Richard would move the world. Shawn would not.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>“You drive,”&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>Shawn can smell shame.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>“Don’t want your boyfriend to see you looking so glamorous?” He smiles and jabs me with his finger. He is looking at me strangely, as if to say, This is who you are. You’ve been pretending that you’re someone else. Someone better. But you are just this.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>I go with him into the bright lights. I laugh as we pass through aisle after aisle, gathering the things he wants to buy. I laugh at every word he says, trying to convince anyone who might have been in the parking lot that it was all a joke. I’m walking on a sprained ankle, but the pain barely registers.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>Dad sees nothing.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>I ask myself questions. Why didn’t he stop when I begged him? It was like getting beaten by a zombie, I write. Like he couldn’t hear me.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>Was it really fun and games? I write. Could he not tell he was hurting me? I don’t know. I just don’t know.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>It’s comforting to think the defect is mine, because that means it is under my power.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>There was one point when he was forcing me from the car, that he had both hands pinned above my head and my shirt rose up. I asked him to let me fix it but it was like he couldn’t hear me. He just stared at it like a great big jerk. It’s a good thing I’m as small as I am. If I was larger, at that moment, I would have torn him apart.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>my humiliation was the cause of that pleasure&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>I retrieved my journal and I wrote another entry, opposite the first, in which I revised the memory. It was a misunderstanding, I wrote. If I’d asked him to stop, he would have.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>Not knowing for certain, but refusing to give way to those who claim certainty, was a privilege I had never allowed myself. My life was narrated for me by others. Their voices were forceful, emphatic, absolute. It had never occurred to me that my voice might be as strong as theirs.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>I could not be near any man without despising myself.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>one that was less about actions and more about essence. It was not that I had done something wrong so much as that I existed in the wrong way. There was something impure in the fact of my being.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>It’s strange how you give the people you love so much power over you, I had written in my journal. But Shawn had more power over me than I could possibly have imagined. He had defined me to myself, and there’s no greater power than that.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>Shawn played the same games with her he’d played with Sadie, testing his control. She never failed to follow his orders, quivering when he raised his voice, apologizing when he screamed at her. That their marriage would be manipulative and violent&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>I have so many bills I can’t imagine how I’m going to pay them. But God will provide either trials for growth or the means to succeed.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>The check was in my hand. I was so tempted, the pain in my jaw so savage, that I must have held it for ten seconds before passing it back.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>When I called Shawn and asked who he’d sold Bud to, he mumbled something vague about a guy passing through from Tooele.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>He pulled out his wallet, opened it and extracted a crisp hundred-dollar bill.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>I BELIEVED THAT HUNDRED dollars was a sign from God.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>She knew I was lying—I could tell because when Dad came in unexpectedly and asked why she was copying the returns, she said the duplicates were for her records.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>He never asked why I’d been sneaking into my own house at three in the morning, and I never asked who he’d been waiting for, sitting up in the middle of the night, with a loaded pistol.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>“Look, honey,” she said. “You get that much because that’s how much you get. Cash it or don’t, it’s up to you.”&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>I’d believed the money would be used to control me, but what it did was enable me to keep my word to myself: for the first time, when I said I would never again work for my father, I believed it.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>I never uttered the words “I’m from Idaho” until I’d left it.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>I began to experience the most powerful advantage of money: the ability to think of things besides money.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>My textbooks began to make sense, and I found myself doing more than the required reading.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>bipolar disorder&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This is my father, I wrote in my notes. He’s describing Dad.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>Ruby Ridge&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>Ruby Ridge, Idaho&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>Randy Weaver and a number of Federal agencies, including the U.S. Marshals Service and the FBI.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>the shooting of a boy, then of his father, then of his mother. The Government had murdered the entire family, parents and children, to cover up what they had done.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>Randy Weaver was arrested&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>blasting the government’s callous disregard for life&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>Randy Weaver had been interviewed by major news organizations and had even co-written a book with his daughter. He now made his living speaking at gun shows.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>Why had federal agents surrounded Randy Weaver’s cabin in the first place?&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>Why had Randy been targeted?&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>the conflict had begun when Randy sold two sawed-off shotguns to an undercover agent he’d met at an Aryan Nations gathering.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>white supremacy was at the heart of this story, not homeschool.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>Dad must have read about Ruby Ridge or seen it on the news, and somehow as it passed through his feverish brain, it had ceased to be a story about someone else and had become a story about him.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>irst, because they are genetically predisposed to mood disorders&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>second, because of the stressful environment and poor parenting of parents with such disorders&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>he kept on believing himself right—after the first car crash, after the second, after the bin, the fire, the pallet. And it was us who paid.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>not about the car, but about the Weavers.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>Why are you like this?&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>Why did you terrify us like that?&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>Why did you fight so hard against made-up monsters, but do nothing about the monsters in your own house?&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>If I could just pretend to be normal for a little while, maybe it would feel like the truth.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>Given the choice between seeing an evil socialist doctor, and admitting to my boyfriend that I believed doctors were evil socialists, I chose to see the doctor.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>You’re positive for strep and mono. Only person I’ve seen in a month to get both.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>There I was, in the heart of the Medical Establishment, and I wanted to see, at long last, what it was I had always been afraid of. Would my eyes bleed? My tongue fall out? Surely something awful would happen. I needed to know what.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>She hadn’t sent any remedies for the strep or the mono. Only for the penicillin.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr></description></item><item><title>Book 18 Sessions 10</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-sessions-10/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 11:15:39 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-sessions-10/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="notes">Notes&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-17-to-keep-it-holy">Chapter 17: To Keep it Holy&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>She is in a totally new environment.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Will you encourage your child to talk more in a new environment?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>As parents, we&amp;rsquo;d better not to choose friends for our child.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>inner peace and Japanese culture （躺平）&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-18-blood-and-feathers">Chapter 18: Blood and Feathers&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated/chapter-18-blood-and-feathers" target="_blank">
Summary &amp;amp; Analysis
&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>New friend: Vanessa&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-19-in-the-beginning">Chapter 19: In the beginning&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated/chapter-19-in-the-beginning" target="_blank">
Summary &amp;amp; Analysis
&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Do you think Tara had some difficulties with her relationship with Charles?&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>The next week, &lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated/characters/tara-westover" target="_blank">
Tara
&lt;/a> drives to the nearest Walmart and buys some women’s clothing.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“We arrived at his house. Charles turned on the TV and settled onto the sofa; I perched lightly on one side. The lights dimmed, the opening credits rolled. Charles inched toward me, slowly at first, then more confidently, until his leg brushed mine. In my mind I bolted, I ran a thousand miles in a single heartbeat. In reality I merely flinched. Charles flinched, too—I’d startled him. I repositioned myself, driving my body into the sofa arm, gathering my limbs and pressing them away from him. I held that unnatural pose for perhaps twenty seconds, until he understood, hearing the words I couldn’t say, and moved to the floor.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Tara learned something from her roommate&lt;/li>
&lt;li>She is not satatified with herself.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Common sense is not common sense.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Sugguestion for girls: Keep smiling and don&amp;rsquo;t say anything.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Though Charles deeply cares for Tara, she’s unable to move their relationship to the next level out of fears, insecurities, and self-hating behaviors instilled in her by years of emotional and verbal abuse at the hands of Gene and Shawn.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-20-recitals-of-the-fathers">Chapter 20: Recitals of the Fathers&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated/chapter-20-recitals-of-the-fathers" target="_blank">
Summary &amp;amp; Analysis
&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated/characters/charles" target="_blank">
Charles
&lt;/a> is &lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated/characters/tara-westover" target="_blank">
Tara
&lt;/a>’s first real, true friend from “that other world”—the world her &lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated/characters/gene-westover-dad" target="_blank">
father
&lt;/a> has been trying to “protect” her from all her life.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Shawn begins calling Tara horrible nicknames like “wench,” “Wilbur,” and “nigger.” None of these nicknames are new, but now that Tara has been to college and learned about the history of slavery, Jim Crow, segregation, and racism in America, she is particularly upset by Shawn’s casual use of the word “nigger.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>How ignorant&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Only my ears are different&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-21-skullcap">Chapter 21: Skullcap&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated/chapter-21-skullcap" target="_blank">
Summary &amp;amp; Analysis
&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The challenge from the professor&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Adaptive&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Failed and tried again&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Full score to get A.&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“I said it did. It was a long shot, but I was the queen of long shots. I called Charles. I told him I was coming to Idaho for Thanksgiving and I needed an algebra tutor. He said he would meet me at Buck’s Peak.”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Excerpt From: Tara Westover. “Educated.” Apple Books.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h1 id="next-session">Next session&lt;/h1>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Homework: Finish the chapter 22 - 24&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Host Volunteer: Shuuka&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Book 18 Sessions 9</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-sessions-9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 12:01:46 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-sessions-9/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="notes">Notes&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-15">Chapter 15&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated/chapter-15-no-more-a-child" target="_blank">
Summary &amp;amp; Analysis
&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Tara&amp;rsquo;s mother: support her husband and support/protect her children&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Sympathy for her mother&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Mother quietly, urgently tells Tara that she shouldn’t “let anything stop [her] from going,” but as Dad’s footsteps approach the kitchen, Mother hurriedly turns back to her work.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>She has married the man, and that&amp;rsquo;s her faith.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Divorce: maybe impossible at all&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Struggle between the husband and &amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Conflict between &amp;hellip;, rational, very difficult to change&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Fatal?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>find the good balance between &amp;hellip; and &amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Compromise?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Question: if get divorced.
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Education&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Future family&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Divorce rate is so high in China? if having more than 1 child&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Two extreme
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Keep the marriage&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Get the rid of another guy&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Gene loves her daughter in his own way&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-16-disloyal-man-disobedient-heaven">Chapter 16: Disloyal Man, Disobedient Heaven&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated/chapter-16-disloyal-man-disobedient-heaven" target="_blank">
Summary &amp;amp; Analysis
&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Tara called her dad, but &amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>BYU&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Tyler: might be easier&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Tara tries reading it, but is unable to distinguish the fictional story of Jean Valjean from the very real backdrop of the French Revolution—she is uncertain of which parts of the story are true and which are false.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h1 id="next-session">Next session&lt;/h1>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Homework: Finish Ch17 - Ch21&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Host Volunteer: Mia &amp;amp; Jizu&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Book 18 Sessions 8</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-sessions-8/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 12:17:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-sessions-8/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="notes">Notes&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-12-fish-eyes">Chapter 12 Fish Eyes&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;code>Siddle Lister&lt;/code> -&amp;gt; &lt;code>Fish Eyes&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-13">Chapter 13&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated/chapter-13-silence-in-the-churches" target="_blank">
Chapter Summary
&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Shawn is systematically attempting to break Tara down and exert control over her by diminishing and even demonizing her.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>PUA: pick-up and play with&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Shawn doesn&amp;rsquo;t know how to express his love to Tara.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Shawn really care Tara.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Instinct&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Sadie: not taking her seriously&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Shawn is violent, possessive, and vengeful.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>The next day, Tara goes to the hardware store and buys a bolt for her bedroom door.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-14">Chapter 14&lt;/h2>
&lt;h2 id="todos">TODOs&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>share the mindmap file&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h1 id="next-session">Next session&lt;/h1>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Homework: Finish Ch15 &amp;amp; Ch16&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Host Volunteer: Jizu&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Book 18 Sessions 7</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-sessions-7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 12:26:47 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-sessions-7/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="notes">Notes&lt;/h1>
&lt;h1 id="next-session">Next session&lt;/h1>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Homework: Finish Ch13 &amp;amp; Ch14&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Host Volunteer: Mia and Giselle&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Book 18 Sessions 6</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-sessions-6/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 12:26:47 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-sessions-6/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="notes">Notes&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-9-perfect-in-his-generation">Chapter 9: Perfect in His Generation&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Refer to the &lt;a href="https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-sessions-5/#chapter-9-perfect-in-his-generation" target="_blank">
excerpts
&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>A friend from another world.
Lunch with collegues to get updated&lt;/p>
&lt;p>His father will be the hero if he successfully predicted the catastrophy.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="ch10-shield-of-feather">Ch10: Shield of Feather&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>prophecy&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Cognitive bias&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The psychology research?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Grandma refused to quit chemotherapy&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Chiropractor&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h1 id="next-session">Next session&lt;/h1>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Homework: Finish Ch11 &amp;amp; Ch12&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Host Volunteer: foo &amp;amp; bar&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Book 18 Sessions 5</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-sessions-5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 09:55:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-sessions-5/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="notes">Notes&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-7-the-lord-will-provide">Chapter 7: The Lord Will Provide&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>His father is calm&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Treatment is very simple.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-8-tiny-harlots">Chapter 8: Tiny Harlots&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated/chapter-8-tiny-harlots" target="_blank">
Litcharts - Chapter Summary &amp;amp; Analysis
&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>har·lot | ˈhärlət | &lt;strong>noun&lt;/strong> &lt;em>archaic&lt;/em> a prostitute.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>• dated, derogatory a woman who has many casual sexual encounters or relationships.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h3 id="playing-piano">Playing Piano&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“People at church said Mary could play the piano beautifully. They used the word “professional.” I didn’t know what that meant until one Sunday when Mary played a piano solo for the congregation. The music stopped my breath. I’d heard the piano played countless times before, to accompany hymns, but when Mary played it, the sound was nothing like that formless clunking. It was liquid, it was air. It was rock one moment and wind the next.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The next day, when Mary returned from the school, I asked her if instead of money she would give me lessons. We perched on the piano bench and she showed me a few finger exercises. Then she asked what else I was learning besides the piano. Dad had told me what to say when people asked about my schooling. “I do school every day,” I said.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Tara is talented in music, and like music a lot.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Very curious&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Give up a bit of money&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="dancing">Dancing&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“She’d misunderstood. She thought I didn’t have money. “It isn’t modest,” I said. Her lips parted in surprise. These Californian Moyles, I thought.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Modest:&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“The other girls rarely spoke to me, but I loved being there with them. I loved the sensation of conformity. Learning to dance felt like learning to belong. I could memorize the movements and, in doing so, step into their minds, lunging when they lunged, reaching my arms upward in time with theirs. Sometimes, when I glanced at the mirror and saw the tangle of our twirling forms, I couldn’t immediately discern myself in the crowd. It didn’t matter that I was wearing a gray T-shirt—a goose among swans. We moved together, a single flock.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Tara got connected with other people (social people)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Not isolated, being in a group of people&lt;/li>
&lt;li>a goose among swans&lt;/li>
&lt;li>belonging&lt;/li>
&lt;li>自卑 not confident&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“The music ended. The girls glared at me as we left the stage—I had ruined the performance—but I could barely see them. Only one person in that room felt real to me, and that was Dad. I searched the audience and recognized him easily. He was standing in the back, the lights from the stage flickering off his square glasses. His expression was stiff, impassive, but I could see anger in it.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>The dad had a great influence on her.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Because of her father&amp;rsquo;s presence&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Maybe a disater&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Honorable girl, still managed&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Parent are not aware of their mistakes. (saving her daughter)&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“The rest of the night was taken up by my father’s lecture. He said Caroline’s class was one of Satan’s deceptions, like the public school, because it claimed to be one thing when really it was another. It claimed to teach dance, but instead it taught immodesty, promiscuity. Satan was shrewd, Dad said. By calling it “dance,” he had convinced good Mormons to accept the sight of their daughters jumping about like whores in the Lord’s house. That fact offended Dad more than anything else: that such a lewd display had taken place in a church.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Dance suit, should be modest&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Satan was shrewd&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“On the Wednesday after Caroline called Mother, I arrived at Papa Jay’s a few minutes early. The younger class had just finished, and the store was flooded with six-year-olds, prancing for their mothers in red velvet hats and skirts sparkling with sequins of deep scarlet. I watched them wiggle and leap through the aisles, their thin legs covered only by sheer tights. I thought they looked like tiny harlots.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h3 id="singing">Singing&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“MOTHER MUST HAVE FELT guilty after the recital, because in the weeks that followed she searched for something else I could do, something Dad wouldn’t forbid. She’d noticed the hours I spent in my room with Tyler’s old boom box, listening to the Mormon Tabernacle Choir, so she began looking for a voice teacher. It took a few weeks to find one, and another few weeks to persuade the teacher to take me. The lessons were much more expensive than the dance class had been, but Mother paid for them with the money she made selling oils.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>She loved the girl, and tried her best to help her daughter.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>mindful about&lt;/li>
&lt;li>paying very high attention on her daughter&lt;/li>
&lt;li>balance very well&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“Mother played the introduction. The music paused; it was time to sing. I might have had any number of thoughts at that moment. I might have thought of my teacher and her techniques—square stance, straight back, dropped jaw. Instead I thought of Tyler, and of lying on the carpet next to his desk, staring at his woolen-socked feet while the Mormon Tabernacle Choir chanted and trilled. He’d filled my head with their voices, which to me were more beautiful than anything except Buck’s Peak.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“Dad smiled at everyone. There was scarcely a person in the church that Dad hadn’t called a gentile—for visiting a doctor or for sending their kids to the public school—but that day he seemed to forget about California socialism and the Illuminati. He stood next to me, a hand on my shoulder, graciously collecting compliments. “We’re very blessed,” he kept saying. “Very blessed.” Papa Jay crossed the chapel and paused in front of our pew. He said I sang like one of God’s own angels. Dad looked at him for a moment, then his eyes began to shine and he shook Papa Jay’s hand like they were old friends.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Very big success&lt;/li>
&lt;li>totally different from the dancing&lt;/li>
&lt;li>church event&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“I’ll find the money,” he told Mother when they went to bed that night. “You get her to that audition.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-9-perfect-in-his-generation">Chapter 9: Perfect in His Generation&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated/chapter-9-perfect-in-his-generations" target="_blank">
LitCharts - Summary and Analysis
&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="dad-called-it-y2k">Dad called it Y2K.&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“The summer I sang the lead for Annie it was 1999. My father was in serious preparedness mode. Not since I was five, and the Weavers were under siege, had he been so certain that the Days of Abomination were upon us.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Dad called it Y2K. On January 1, he said, computer systems all over the world would fail. There would be no electricity, no telephones. All would sink into chaos, and this would usher in the Second Coming of Christ.
”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“Can’t they fix it?”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>“Nope, can’t be done,” Dad said. “Man trusted his own strength, and his strength was weak.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h3 id="at-the-worm-creek-opera-house">At the Worm Creek Opera House&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“I’d never learned how to talk to people who weren’t like us—people who went to school and visited the doctor. Who weren’t preparing, every day, for the End of the World. Worm Creek was full of these people, people whose words seemed ripped from another reality. That was how it felt the first time the director spoke to me, like he was speaking from another dimension. All he said was, “Go find FDR.” I didn’t move.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>He tried again. “President Roosevelt. FDR.”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>“Is that like a JCB?” I said. “You need a forklift?”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Everyone laughed.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h3 id="a-friend-called-charlies">A friend called Charlies&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“I’m Charles,” he said. There was a pause while he waited for me to give my name, but I didn’t. “I saw you in the last play,” he said after a moment. “I wanted to tell you something.” I braced myself, for what I wasn’t sure, then he said, “I wanted to tell you that your singing is about the best I ever heard.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“Maybe,” I said, and he smiled. A few of his friends stepped into the wing and called to him. He stood and said goodbye, and I watched him join them, taking in the easy way they joked together and imagining an alternate reality in which I was one of them. I imagined Charles inviting me to his house, to play a game or watch a movie, and felt a rush of pleasure. But when I pictured Charles visiting Buck’s Peak, I felt something else, something like panic. What if he found the root cellar? What if he discovered the fuel tank? Then I understood, finally, what the rifle was for. That mighty barrel, with its special range that could reach from the mountain to the valley, was a defensive perimeter for the house, for our supplies, because Dad said we would be driving when everyone else was hotfooting it. We would have food, too, when everyone else was starving, looting. Again I imagined Charles climbing the hill to our house. But in my imagination I was on the ridge, and I was watching his approach through crosshairs.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h3 id="y2k-problem-didnt-happen">Y2K problem didn&amp;rsquo;t happen&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>I waited for the screen to flicker and die. I was trying to take it all in, this last, luxurious moment—of sharp yellow light, of warm air flowing from the heater. I was experiencing nostalgia for the life I’d had before, which I would lose at any second, when the world turned and began to devour itself.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The longer I sat motionless, breathing deeply, trying to inhale the last scent of the fallen world, the more I resented its continuing solidity. […] Sometime after 1:30 I went to bed. I glimpsed Dad as I left, his face frozen in the dark, the light from the TV leaping across his square glasses.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>He seemed smaller to me than he had that morning. The disappointment in his features was so childlike, for a moment I wondered how God could deny him this. He, a faithful servant, who suffered willingly just as Noah had willingly suffered to build the ark.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But God withheld the flood.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="themes">Themes&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="devoutness-and-delusionhttpswwwlitchartscomliteducatedthemesdevoutness-and-delusion">&lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated/themes/devoutness-and-delusion" target="_blank">
Devoutness and Delusion
&lt;/a>&lt;/h3>
&lt;h3 id="family-abuse-and-entrapmenthttpswwwlitchartscomliteducatedthemesfamily-abuse-and-entrapment">&lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated/themes/family-abuse-and-entrapment" target="_blank">
Family, Abuse, and Entrapment
&lt;/a>&lt;/h3>
&lt;h3 id="memory-history-and-subjectivityhttpswwwlitchartscomliteducatedthemesmemory-history-and-subjectivity">&lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated/themes/memory-history-and-subjectivity" target="_blank">
Memory, History, and Subjectivity
&lt;/a>&lt;/h3>
&lt;h1 id="next-session">Next session&lt;/h1>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Homework: Finish Ch9, Ch10&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Host Volunteer: Samantha
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Questions&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Excerpts&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Book 18 Sessions 4</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-sessions-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 12:20:11 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-sessions-4/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="notes">Notes&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-5-honest-dirt">Chapter 5: Honest Dirt&lt;/h2>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>That pace would never be possible in the public school. You can only do that at home, where you can sit down and really focus, with no distractions.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Morse Code&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-6-shield-and-buckler">Chapter 6: Shield and Buckler&lt;/h2>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>I’d found a hard hat in the shop, but Dad took that, too. “You’ll move slower trying to balance this silly thing on your head,” he said.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h1 id="next-session">Next session&lt;/h1>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Homework: Finish Ch 7 - Ch9&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Host Volunteer: Jizu, Giselle&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Book 18 Session 3</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-session-3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 12:21:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-session-3/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="notes">Notes&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Chapter 3 &amp;amp; 4&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="grandam-over-in-town">Grandam-over-in-town&lt;/h2>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Faye forever removed and isolated herself - and her children - from her own family&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="taras-father-gene">Tara&amp;rsquo;s Father, Gene&lt;/h2>
&lt;h2 id="grandma-down-the-hill">Grandma-down-the-hill&lt;/h2>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“What was happening now had happened before. This was the second severing of mother and daughter. The tape was playing in a loop.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>diversity for the family members&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Illuminati &lt;a href="https://zh.wikipedia.org/wiki/%E5%85%89%E7%85%A7%E6%B4%BE" target="_blank">
光照派
&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“According to Grandma, a hundred years ago a tribe of Apaches had fought the U.S. Cavalry on those faded rocks. The tribe was outnumbered: the battle lost, the war over. All that was left to do was wait to die. Soon after the battle began, the warriors became trapped on a ledge. Unwilling to suffer a humiliating defeat, cut down one by one as they tried to break through the cavalry, they mounted their horses and charged off the face of the mountain. When the Apache women found their broken bodies on the rocks below, they cried huge, desperate tears, which turned to stone when they touched the earth.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="chapter-4">Chapter 4&lt;/h2>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>“Me, I never blamed anyone for the accident, least of all Tyler. It was just one of those things. A decade later my understanding would shift, part of my heavy swing into adulthood, and after that the accident would always make me think of the Apache women, and of all the decisions that go into making a life—the choices people make, together and on their own, that combine to produce any single event. Grains of sand, incalculable, pressing into sediment, then rock.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h1 id="next-session">Next session&lt;/h1>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Homework: Finish Chapter 5 &amp;amp; 6&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Host Volunteer: Shuuka&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Book 18 Session 2</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-session-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 12:19:59 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-session-2/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="notes">Notes&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="q1-how-did-motherfatherme-get-changed-while-mother-became-a-midwife">Q1: How did Mother/father/me get changed while mother became a midwife?&lt;/h2>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Midwifing changed my mother. She was a grown woman with seven children, but this was the first time in her life that she was, without question or caveat, the one in charge. Sometimes, in the days after a birth, I detected in her something of Judy’s heavy presence, in a forceful turn of her head, or the imperious arch of an eyebrow. She stopped wearing makeup, then she stopped apologizing for not wearing it.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>At the beginning, very exhausted&lt;/li>
&lt;li>acted as an assistant&lt;/li>
&lt;li>acted as a midwife herself&lt;/li>
&lt;li>income/money to afford the telephone&lt;/li>
&lt;li>not so boring, help people&lt;/li>
&lt;li>cheaper but illegal&lt;/li>
&lt;li>only in charge&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Offered such a job under such circumstances, accept or not?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>age: 30 or 40 year-old?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>7 children, baby&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Her father really force her mother to work&lt;/li>
&lt;li>As long as we have income, then nobody can force us&lt;/li>
&lt;li>hesitated to make a change&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Every child is different&lt;/li>
&lt;li>stable&lt;/li>
&lt;li>She worked a housewife&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Why did she married such a kind of guy?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>妇产科 （Obstetrics and Gynecology） vs . Midwife&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Harvard Positive Psychology&lt;/li>
&lt;li>survivalist&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Dad stood there for several seconds, his mouth open. Of course a midwife needs a phone, he said. Then he went back to the junkyard and that’s all that was ever said about it. We hadn’t had a telephone for as long as I could remember, but the next day there it was, resting in a lime-green cradle, its glossy finish looking out of place next to the murky jars of cohosh and skullcap.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>She barked orders and we moved wordlessly to follow them. The baby was born without complications. It was mythic and romantic, being an intimate witness to this turn in life’s cycle, but Mother had been right, I didn’t like it. It was long and exhausting, and smelled of groin sweat.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="q2-how-can-we-learn-from-the-midwife-story-to-make-a-change-in-our-life">Q2: How can we learn from the midwife story to make a change in our life?&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Money is the most important thing.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>If you earn above an amount, doesn&amp;rsquo;t make a different. (Survey)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>How to spend the money? For eating or helping others&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>The next time the midwife came she brought her daughter Maria, who stood next to her mother, imitating her movements, with a baby wedged against her wiry nine-year-old frame. I stared hopefully at her. I hadn’t met many other girls like me, who didn’t go to school. I edged closer, trying to draw her attention, but she was wholly absorbed in listening to her mother, who was explaining how cramp bark and motherwort should be administered to treat post-birth contractions. Maria’s head bobbed in agreement; her eyes never left her mother’s face.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>THERE WERE NO HERBALISTS in Wyoming as good as Mother, so a few months after the incident at the hospital, Judy came to Buck’s Peak to restock. The two women chatted in the kitchen, Judy perched on a barstool, Mother leaning across the counter, her head resting lazily in her hand. I took the list of herbs to the storeroom. Maria, lugging a different baby, followed. I pulled dried leaves and clouded liquids from the shelves, all the while gushing about Mother’s exploits, finishing with the confrontation in the hospital. Maria had her own stories about dodging Feds, but when she began to tell one I interrupted her.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>“Judy is a fine midwife,” I said, my chest rising. “But when it comes to doctors and cops, nobody plays stupid like my mother.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h1 id="next-session">Next session&lt;/h1>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Homework: ?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Host Volunteer: ?&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Book 18 Session 1</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-session-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 12:19:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/notes/book-18-session-1/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="game">Game&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>We split the 1st chapter into 3 parts, and 3 teams&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Team 1: Fancy, Ellen&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Team 2: Hongyan, Semantha&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Team 3: Giselle, Mia&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Online: Shuuka, Wendy&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="1st-part">1st part&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Until&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Then I remembered: the big dairy farm a mile north of Buck’s Peak, that was Jim’s.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Children should be guided by the god
Grandma: all children left except Tara' father&lt;/p>
&lt;p>How did Tara&amp;rsquo;s father get educated?
Mother&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Author&amp;rsquo;s father, education, public school&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Dream, imagination&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Religious&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Different versions&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Isaiah&lt;/li>
&lt;li>the solemnity of an oracle&lt;/li>
&lt;li>manicured&lt;/li>
&lt;li>As he slid past us I caught a whiff of manure.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mormons" target="_blank">
Mormons
&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="2nd-part">2nd part&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Until&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>then gunfire, then silence.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Grandma convince me to get away from my father&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Breakfast: seven kids&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Butter or honey&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Breakfast became a test of loyalty.
“Butter and honey shall he eat,” Dad droned, low and monotone, weary from a long day hauling scrap. “That he may know to refuse the evil, and choose the good.”&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>The next morning Dad purged our fridge of milk, yogurt and cheese, and that evening when he came home, his truck was loaded with fifty gallons of honey.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="3rd-part">3rd part&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Until the end of Chapter 1&lt;/p>
&lt;p>She didn&amp;rsquo;t leave finally.
Wounded Knee or Waco
for the Days of Abomination&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>They’re freedom fighters. They wouldn’t let the Government brainwash their kids in them public schools, so the Feds came after them.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://www.sparknotes.com/lit/educated/" target="_blank">
&lt;a href="https://www.sparknotes.com/lit/educated/">https://www.sparknotes.com/lit/educated/&lt;/a>
&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated" target="_blank">
&lt;a href="https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated">https://www.litcharts.com/lit/educated&lt;/a>
&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h1 id="next-session">Next session&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Finish the 2nd chapter&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Book 18 Candidates</title><link>https://english-reading-club.github.io/news/book-18-candidates/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 10:01:03 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://english-reading-club.github.io/news/book-18-candidates/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="book-18-non-fiction">Book 18: Non-Fiction&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="candidate-1-educated-a-memoir-by-tara-westover">Candidate 1: Educated: A Memoir by Tara Westover&lt;/h3>
&lt;pre>&lt;code>Tara Westover - Educated_ A Memoir-Random House (2018).epub
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;p>Buy:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B072BLVM83" target="_blank">
Amazon
&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="e-book-preview">E-book Preview&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://sap.sharepoint.com/teams/EnglishReadingClubChina/Shared%20Documents/Book%20Candidates" target="_blank">
SAP Sharepoint
&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>持续更新的下一本书意向清单，欢迎随时添加: &lt;a href="https://sap.sharepoint.com/teams/DBSLibrary/_layouts/15/Doc.aspx?OR=teams&amp;amp;action=edit&amp;amp;sourcedoc=%7bDBA1A588-306A-4133-8438-55F8BDE9EFEE%7d" target="_blank">
SAP Excel Online
&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://english-reading-club.github.io/BookClubPoster_20210324_Educated.jpg" alt="Poster">&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>